today
I've said a lot about you seriously believe it
look at this bro
now we are going to jump at an event
at the invitation of Felipe Tito
but if he is Asian
all right
is I fall into the world
I think it's
thank you dear
I'm feeling a little out of place
you're feeling it fucking
ah hidden right brother
it's us brother
I'm hungry here
good night
1 more time
high pretense
try to play 1 Charlie Brown in Neymar's hand
haha
today
I've said a lot about you seriously believe it
caraca hand
but you're not from Bradesco no
born
worthless beauty
Charlie Brown
let you know too
it's also at the bank
then go get
very good
then I add you
launch
Charlie Brown
Welcome to the jungle
valeu valeu
fucking crazy bro
dream small
big dreaming is the same thing,
right brother,
you're on
so i will do what
I will choose
I'm going to fall into us
you know what was more painful
when paying there
to command
and then the woman said like this
it was not you at the event
I said I was
oh so it's not good at all
if i knew i would ask for something more right
old bark smoke
is on
that worked